6/4/24, 8:30 AM InfoJobs - CV

# InfoJobs

Por leer en Français | French - Business Development Representative B2B



## Sales professional en Serpasyon SI

CV actualizado el 03/06/2024

Edad: 22 años (19/09/2001)

Vehículo propio: No

Género: Mujer

Madrid ✓ Tú pides: Madrid

Autónomo: No

## Killer questions

#### Quelle expérience avez-vous en travaillant au téléphone en français?

J'ai eu des conversations téléphoniques afin d'administrer les contrats et conditions de nos clients. Avec cette expérience j'ai eu aussi des conversations et négociations pour fidéliser les clients à notre entreprise.



#### Experiencias

Septiembre 2022 - Mayo 2024 (1 año y 8 meses)

### Sales professional

Serpasyon SI

Connecting the right asset to each profile, the main objective was to give personalized attention to each customer. Here I also experience in the retail industry. Here some key questions that resonated with my position were: - Attention to detail - Good performance under pressure

Privacy - Terms

6/4/24, 8:30 AM InfoJobs - CV

Marzo 2021 - Julio 2022 (1 año y 4 meses)

#### **Executive assistant**

Mimo Mil SI

Responsible for ensuring the correct connections between our clients and the company Advised and hosted reunions in an international ambiance, communicating with clients that used our platform in France and Spain Revised and elaborated new contracts

#### **Estudios**

Estudios reglados

LICENCIATURA

Junio 2024 - Junio 2024 (Menos de 1 mes)

## Filología Francesa Universidad Complutense de Madrid

LICENCIATURA

Junio 2024 - Junio 2024 (Menos de 1 mes)

#### Filología Inglesa

Universidad Complutense de Madrid

#### **Idiomas**

Español Nativo

Inglés Nativo

Francés Nativo

#### Preferencias laborales

Puesto deseado Sales representative, Data analyst

Provincia deseada Madrid